<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Termux Guide For Beginners</string>
    <string name="article_text1">:-HACKING INTRODUCTIONS:-</string>
    <string name="article_text2"> <b>What is Hacking:-</b>\n\n
         <b>Hacking</b> is a part of computing for almost six decades and it is a very broad discipline, which covers a wide range of topics..\n\n
<b>Hacking</b> is the act of finding the possible entry points that exist in a computer system or a computer network and finally entering into them.\n\n
        <b>Hacking</b> is usually done to gain unauthorized access to a computer system or a computer network, either to harm the systems or to steal sensitive information available on the computer./n/n
<b>Hacking</b> is usually legal as long as it is being done to find <b>weaknesses in a computer</b> or network system for testing purpose.
        This sort of hacking is what we call <b>Ethical Hacking</b>.\n\n A computer expert who does the act of hacking is called a <b>"Hacker"</b>. Hackers are those who seek knowledge, to understand how systems operate,how they are designed, and then attempt to play with these systems.
\n\n<b>Purpose of Hacking:- </b> \n\n
There could be various positive and negative intentions behind performing hacking activities.\n\n Here is a list of some probable reasons why people indulge in hacking activities −\n\n
        <b>* Just for fun.</b>\n\n<b>* Show-off.</b>\n\n <b>* Steal important information.</b>\n\n<b>* Damaging the system.</b>\n\n<b>* Hampering privacy.</b>\n\n<b>* Money extortion.</b>\n\n<b>* System security testing.</b>\n\n<b>* To break policy compliance.</b>\n\n
        With the rise of computers and ever-changing technology, hackers have become a strong presence in modern society.\n The very first hackers emerged from <b>MIT in 1969</b>, but back then their main goal was to improve the software and hardware they were working with. \n\n

Since then, hackers have evolved and become more malicious. From hacking major companies, to stealing millions of dollars and revealing government secrets, hackers are now a major part of modern society.
    </string>

    <string name="text3"><b>WHAT IS TERMUX?</b>\n\n Termux is a great tool that allows access to advanced tools without root on your android phone.\nTermux is Command-line based and to use this app the most basic thing you should know is commands.\n\nIn this post we are going to learn about most basic commands in the termux app.\nIf you know all the command below you can easily navigate in termux and please practice this command so you can learn more advanced stuff more easily.\n\nIf you want to know why you must learn termux then check this post.\n\n
        <b>List of all the termux basic commands:</b>\n\nYou can run this command in a sequence to practice and know your self how these commands work on termux.\n\n
        <b>HOW TO INSTALL?</b>\n\n # Update all the packages and dependencies installed on the system:\n\n
        <b>$ apt update\n$ apt upgrade </b>\n\nIf any update is available it will ask you on the terminal if you want to upgrade or not, press Y if you want the update.\n\n
        # Grant storage permission:-\n\n
 <b>$ termux-setup-storage</b>\n\n
now you can access your Storage and all the folder in it using termux.\n\n
        # Know Which directory you are in:-\n\n<b>$ pwd </b>\n\n
# List all the files and directories:\nthis command will show you the folder and files in your current working directory.\n\n <b> $ ls</b>\n\n
        <b># Move forward in directories:-</b>\ncd command allows you to move in a folder just type cd and the folder name you want to move here I am moving in storage.\n\n
 <b>$ cd storage</b>\n\n
        # Move backward in directories:-\n\n<b>$ cd ..</b>\n\n
        <b># Clear Screen:-</b>\nBy typing clear in the termux you can clear all the previous results.\n\n<b>$ clear</b>\n\n
        <b># Create a folder or a directory:-</b>\nMkdir Stand for make directory. Type mkdir and give a space and type folder name and press enter to see the folder you have just created just type ls.\n\n
 <b>$ mkdir folderName</b>\n\n
        <b># Delete a folder or a directory:-</b>\nRmdir stands for Remove Directory.Type rmdir space folder name to remove that folder.\n\n
 <b>$ rmdir folderName</b>\n\n
 <b># Copy a file</b> from one directory to another directory:\n\n
 <b>$ cp files-name file-path</b>\n\n
 You can copy files by typing cp the file name and after giving a space you can type the path where you want to copy the file.\n E.g: <b>cp virus.apk /storage/shared this will copy the virus.apk to the storage/shared folder.</b>\n\n
       <b> # Install a Package:-</b>\nyou can install any package from the list, just type pkg install package-name.\n\n
<b>$ pkg install packageName</b>\n\n
        # Uninstall a Package:-\n\n<b>$ pkg uninstall packageName</b> \n\n
        # Install Python in termux:-\n\n<b>$ pkg install python</b>\n\n
        # Install Git in termux:-\n\n<b>$ pkg install git</b>\n\n
Git will allow you to download any project from the github.\n
# Download projects from GitHub repository :\n\n<b>$ git clone Link-of-the-project</b>\n\n
e.g: <b>$ git clone https://github.com/adi1090x/termux-style.git</b>\n\n
         # Check the history in termux:-\n\n
 <b>$ history</b>\n\n
       <b> # Create a text file in termux:-</b>\n
first, you have to download a package name nano.\n\n<b>$ pkg install nano</b> \n\n
Type nano on the terminal.\nType anything you want I am typing <b>hello world</b>\n\n
Press <b>CTRL+X</b> and press Y to save the file.\n
# Give the file name <b>anyname.txt</b> and press enter.\n
Type ls command to see your directory.\n\n
        # See whats inside a text file:- \n\n<b>$ cat file-name</b>\n\n
# Run this command and everything in the text file will be printed on the terminal.\n\n
        # Delete a file in termux:-\n\n<b>$ rm file-name</b>\ne.g: <b>rm data.txt</b>\n\n
        <b># List all the Packages in termux:-</b>\nBy Using this command You will be able to see all the installed packages in your termux app.\n\n<b>$                apt list</b>\n\n\n

                <b>--------------- THANK U --------------</b>.

    </string>
    <string name="text4"><b>How to protect yourself from Hackers:-</b>\n\n

<b>1)- Don’t access</b> personal or financial data with public Wi-Fi.\n\n
This may seem like a no-brainer, but you’d be surprised how many people check their bank accounts or make purchases with a credit card while using public Wi-Fi. It’s best to do those things on a secure connection.\n\n
<b>2)- Turn off</b> anything you don’t need.\n\n
Hackers can use certain features on your phone to get at your information, location or connection. So, instead of keeping your GPS, wireless connection and geo-tracking on all the time, just turn them on when you need them.\n\n
<b>3)- Choose your apps</b> wisely.\n\n
Only download apps from trustworthy sources that have established a good reputation. Make sure you update your software and apps regularly and get rid of old apps you don’t use.\n\n
 <b>4)- Use a password,</b> lock code or encryption.\n\n
Make sure your passwords are at least eight characters long, with a mix of upper and lower case, and include numbers or other characters, and never use the auto-complete feature for passwords.\n\n You can use the storage encryption feature on your phone to protect your private data, and set your screen to timeout after five minutes or less.\n\n
 <b>5)- Be skeptical</b> about links and attachments.\n\n
If you’re not sure about the source, don’t use the link or open the attachment.\n\n
<b>6)- Trace or erase.</b>\n\n
Make sure your data is secure if your mobile device is stolen or lost. You can set up your device to lock itself after a pre-set number of failed log-in attempts.\n\n
<b> Basic Phone Security Tips:-</b>\n\n
<b>7)- Never leave</b> your phone unattended. Keeping your phone with you at all times while in a public place is the first, best rule to follow.\n\n
<b>8)- Change your</b> phone’s default passcode. Your phone likely comes with a simple, predictable default password, and those who know can use this to their advantage.\n\n Change your code to something more complex, and resist the usual "1234," "0000" and “2580” codes that are commonly used.\n\n
<b>9)- Manage your Bluetooth</b> Security. Avoid using unprotected Bluetooth networks and turn off your Bluetooth service when you aren’t using it.\n\n
<b>10)- Protect your PIN</b> and Credit Card data. Use a protected app to store PIN numbers and credit cards, or better yet, don’t store them in your phone at all.\n\n
        <b>Advanced Ways to Prevent Phone Hacking:-</b>\n\n
If you’re still worried about hacking, there are further steps you can take to protect yourself.\n\n
<b>11)- Turn off</b> your autocomplete feature. By doing this, you can prevent stored critical personal data from being accessed.\n\n
<b>12)- Regularly delete</b> your browsing history, cookies, and cache. Removing your virtual footprint is important in minimizing the amount of data that can be harvested by prying eyes.\n\n.
<b>13)- Use a security</b> app that increases protection.\n Webroot offers the all-in-one Mobile Security for Android app that provides antivirus protection and allows you to remotely locate, lock up and wipe your phone in the event you lose track of it.\n\n\N
<b>---------------- THANK YOU ----------------</b>


    </string>
    <string name="text5">
        <b>lIST OF TOP HACKERS:-</b>\n\n
        Here are some of the most infamous and nefarious <b>“black hatters”</b> what they did to earn their reputations, and where they are today.\n\n

<b>1. Kevin Mitnick:-</b>\n\n
The US Department of Justice called him the <b>“most wanted computer criminal in US history.”</b>\n Kevin Mitnick’s story is so wild that it was even the basis for a featured film called Track Down.\n\n
<b>What did he do?</b>\n\n
After serving a year in prison for hacking into the Digital Equipment Corporation’s network, he was let out for three years of supervised release.\n But near the end of that period, he fled and went on a 2.5-year hacking spree that involved breaching the national defense warning system and stealing corporate secrets.\n\n
<b>Where is he now?</b>\n\n
Mitnick was eventually caught and convicted with a five-year prison sentence.\n After fully serving those years, he became a consultant and public speaker for computer security. He now runs Mitnick Security Consulting, LLC.\n\n
<b>2. Jonathan James</b>\n\n
The story of Jonathan James, known as “c0mrade,” is a tragic one.\n He began hacking at a young age, managing to hack into several commercial and government networks and being sent to prison for it—all while he was still a minor.\n\n
<b>What did he do?</b>\n\n
James eventually hacked into NASA’s network and downloaded enough source code (assets equaling $1.7 million at the time) to learn how the International Space Station worked.\n\n NASA had to shut down its network for three entire weeks while they investigated the breach, costing an additional $41,000.\n\n
<b>Where is he now?</b>\n\n
In 2007, several high-profile companies fell victim to numerous malicious network attacks. Even though James denied any involvement, he was suspected and investigated.\n\n In 2008, James committed suicide, believing he would be convicted of crimes he didn’t commit.\n\n
<b>3. Albert Gonzalez:-</b>\n\n
Albert Gonzalez started off as the leader of a hacker group called ShadowCrew.\n In addition to stealing and selling credit card numbers, ShadowCrew also fabricated fraudulent passports, health insurance cards, and birth certificates for identity theft crimes.\n\n
6 Warning Signs Of Digital Identity Theft You Should not IgnoreIdentity theft is not too rare of an occurrence these days, yet we often fall into the trap of thinking that it will always happen to "someone else". Do not ignore the warning signs.\n\n
<b>What did he do?</b>\n\n
Albert Gonzalez paved his way to internet fame when he collected more than 170 million credit card and ATM card numbers over a period of two years.\n\n He then hacked into the databases of TJX Companies and Heartland Payment Systems to steal all of their stored credit card numbers as well.\n\n
<b>Where is he now?</b>\n\n
Gonzalez was sentenced to prison for 20 years (two sentences of 20 years to be served simultaneously) and is scheduled for release in 2025.\n\n
<b>4. Kevin Poulsen:-</b>\n\n
Kevin Poulsen, also known as “Dark Dante,” earned his 15 minutes of fame by utilizing his intricate knowledge of telephone systems.\n\n At one point, he hacked a radio station’s phone lines and fixed himself as the winning caller, earning him a brand new Porsche. According to media, he was the “Hannibal Lecter of computer crime.”\n\n
<b>What did he do?</b>\n\n
Poulsen got himself onto the FBI’s wanted list when he hacked into federal systems and stole wiretap information.\n\n He was later captured in a supermarket (of all places) and sentenced to 51 months in prison and a bill for $56,000 in restitution.\n\n
<b>Where is he now?</b>\n\n
Poulsen changed his ways after being released from prison in 1995.\n He began working as a journalist and is now a contributing editor for Wired.\n In 2006, he even helped law enforcement to identify 744 sex offenders on MySpace.\n\n
<b>5.Nasa Hacker Gary McKinnon:-</b>\n\n
Gary McKinnon, known as “Solo” on the internet, allegedly coordinated what would become the largest military computer hack of all time.\n\n
<b>What did he do?</b>\n\n
Over a 13-month period from February 2001 to March 2002, McKinnon illegally accessed 97 computers belonging to the US Armed Forces and NASA.\n
He claimed he was only searching for information on free energy suppression and UFO cover-ups.\n\n According to US authorities he deleted a number of critical files and rendered over 300 computers inoperable, resulting in over $700,000 in damages.\n\n
<b>Where is he now?</b>\n\n
Being of Scottish descent and operating out of the United Kingdom, McKinnon was able to dodge the American government until 2005, when he faced extradition.\n\n After a series of appeals, Theresa May blocked his extradition on the grounds that he was “seriously ill” and that extradition would be “incompatible with [his] human rights.”\n\n
<b>6. Robert Tappan Morris:- </b>\n\n
Robert Tappan Morris picked up his knowledge of computers from his father Robert Morris, who was a computer scientist at Bell Labs and later the NSA.\n\n Morris is credited as the creator of the world’s first known computer worm.\n\n
<b>What did he do?</b>\n\n
In 1988, he created the Morris Worm while he was a student at Cornell University. \nThe program was intended to gauge the size of the internet, but it had a flaw: computers could be infected multiple times, and each infection would cause the computer to slow down even more. It rendered over 6,000 computers unusable.\n\n
7 Types of Computer Viruses to Watch Out For and What They DoMany types of computer viruses can steal or destroy your data.\n Here are some of the most common viruses and what they do.\n\n
<b>Where is he now?</b>\n\n
In 1989, Robert Tappan Morris was found to have violated the Computer Fraud and Abuse Act. He was sentenced to three years of probation, 400 hours of community service, and a $10,050 fine.\n\n He eventually founded Y Combinator and is now a tenured professor at Massachusetts Institute of Technology.\n\n
<b>7. Loyd Blankenship:-</b>\n\n
Loyd Blankenship, known as “The Mentor” in hacking circles, has been an active hacker since the 1970s.\n He was a member of several hacking groups in the past, most notably Legion of Doom (LOD).\n\n
<b>What did he do?</b>\n\n
Blankenship authored an essay called “Mentor’s Last Words” (also called “Conscience of a Hacker and Hacker Manifesto”), which he wrote after being arrested in 1986.\n The essay has come to be seen as a kind of cornerstone for hacking culture.\n\n
<b>Where is he now?</b>\n\n
Blankenship was hired by Steve Jackson Games in 1989 to work on GURPS Cyberpunk.\n The US Secret Service raided his home in 1990 and confiscated the game’s rulebook, calling it a “handbook for computer crime.”\n He has since given up on hacking and is now the head of product research and design at McAfee.\n\n
<b>8. Julian Assange:-</b>\n\n
Julian Assange began hacking at the age of 16 under the name “Mendax.”\n Over four years, he hacked into various government, corporate, and educational networks—including the Pentagon, NASA, Lockheed Martin, Citibank, and Stanford University.\n\n
<b>What did he do?</b>\n\n
Assange went on to create WikiLeaks in 2006 as a platform for publishing news leaks and classified documents from anonymous sources.\n\n The United States launched an investigation against Assange in 2010 to charge him under the Espionage Act of 1917.\n\n
<b>Where is he now?</b>\n\n
Assange is currently a citizen of Ecuador and holed up in the Ecuadorian embassy in London, fearing extradition to the United States.\n\n

<b>9. Guccifer 2.0:-</b>\n\n
Who is Guccifer 2.0? Nobody knows for sure. It could be a person, or a group masquerading as a person.\n The name pays homage to a Romanian hacker (known as “Guccifer”) who often targeted US government officials and others of political prominence.\n\n
<b>What did they do?</b>\n\n
During the 2016 US Presidential Election, the Democratic National Convention’s network was hacked.\n Thousands of documents were leaked on WikiLeaks and elsewhere.\n Many believe that Guccifer 2.0 is a cover for Russian intelligence, but in an interview with Vice, Guccifer 2.0 claimed he was Romanian and not Russian.\n\n
<b>Where are they now?</b>\n\n
Guccifer 2.0 disappeared just before the 2016 US Presidential Election, then reappeared once in January 2017 to assert that he had no ties to Russian intelligence.\n\n
        <b>10. Anonymous:-</b>\n\n
Anonymous may be the most well-known hacker of all time, yet also the most nebulous.\n\n Anonymous is not a single person but rather a decentralized group of hackers with no true membership or hierarchy. Anybody can act in the name of Anonymous.\n\n

<b>What did they do?</b>\n\n
Since their debut in 2003, Anonymous has been credited for attacking several notable targets, including Amazon, PayPal, Sony.\n\n The Westboro Baptist Church, the Church of Scientology, parts of the dark web, and the governments of Australia, India, Syria, the United States, among dozens of others.\n\n\n
<b>---------HACKING_COUNTRY:------------</b>\n\n
<b>TOP 10 COUNTRIES WITH MOST HACKERS IN THE WORLD:-</b>\n\n
Cambridge, Massachusetts based cloud platform provider Akamai had studied the global cyber attack traffic in last quarter of 2012 and published a report on the countries with maximum share in global cyber attack.\n\n The article talks about the top 10 countries with maximum share in global cyber attack traffic and the probable reason behind each one of them.\n\n
Following are the top 10 countries with most cyber criminals that have expertise in hacking.\n\n
<b>1. CHINA:-</b>\n\n
Well, it is not a surprise to anyone. Ask any cyber professional and he would name China.\n\n Infact in order to gain superiority over other countries in cyberspace, China has promoted cyber security as a culture thereby having a fairly good cyber literacy among its educated youth.\n\n This has also led to an increase in cybercrime and rise in the number of cyber criminals. According to various estimates 41% of the world’s cyber attacks have their genesis in China.\n It is believed that organized hacker networks are run in China which are supported by People’s Liberation Army of China.\n The purpose is to mostly hack in U.S govt networks and those of its allies.\n\n
<b>2. UNITED STATES:-</b>\n\n
At the recent G20 summit, President of the United States Barack Obama said that U.S has the largest and the best cyber arsenal in the world.\n\n This might be actually true given the sophistication of cyber attacks allegedly carried out by U.S. Remember Stuxnet? Yeah, the same Trojan which was planted into Iranian Nuclear Power Plant to disrupt the centrifuges.\n\n As per various estimated, U.S accounts for nearly 10% of the world’s attack traffic. It is home to many famous and infamous hackers.\n\n

<b>3. TURKEY:-</b>\n\n
Third place is taken by Turkey. In the global cyber attack traffic, Turkey takes a share of 4.7%.\n Turkish hackers have increased their activities in last decade or so.\n\n
<b>4. RUSSIA:-</b>\n\n
The latest DNC hack would place Russia on number 4th in the list.\n This hack has evoked fears of rigging of upcoming U.S Presidential elections by Russian hackers. As per estimates, nearly 4.3% of the global attack traffic is generated from Russia.\n\n Russian hackers are famous worldwide and have a knack for attacking most secure networks like those of Google, Facebook, and Apple.\n\n
<b>5. TAIWAN:-</b>\n\n
Small but not weak must be the motto of Taiwanese hackers. The little island located near China is quite a hub for hackers.\n It’s share in global cyber attacks in nearly 3.7%.\n\n
<b>6. BRAZIL:-</b>\n\n
The recently held olympics at Rio brought the entire world focus on Brazilian hackers.\n With 3.3% share in the global attack traffic, Brazil takes the 6th spot.\n\n Infact Brazil has the highest cyber attack traffic not only in South- America but entire southern hemisphere.\n The reason behind huge number of cyber criminals in Brazil is the cashless nature of its economy.\n A good percentage population of Brazil uses electronic and online payment systems making them vulnerable to hackers.\n\n
<b>7. ROMANIA:-</b>\n\n
At 7th position is Romania taking 3.3% share in the global cyber assault. You would be surprised to know that there is a place in Romania called Ramnicu Valcea which is popularly known as the hub of criminal hackers.\n Most of the cyber attacks from Romania can be traced to this one location.\n\n
<b>8. INDIA:-</b>\n\n
Standing 8th on the list Cyber criminals and hackers in India, the IT hub of the world. In recent times, India is witnessing increasing number of cyber crimes .\n\n Infact the gullible nature of Indians puts them at very high cyber risk which is why Indian tourists are most prone to cyber attacks. The Indian hackers take a share of 2.3% in the global cyber crime.\n\n
<b>9. ITALY:-</b>\n\n
At ninth position in the list of countries with most hackers comes the Italy. About 1.6% of the total cybercrime activities is taken by Italian hackers.\n\nThere are two very famous Italian hackers; Luigi Auriemma and Donato FarranteAureima.\n They are involved in hacking government sites and reveal information publicly regarding any security threats.\n\n
<b>10. HUNGARY:-</b>\n\n
The 10th spot is taken by Hungary. Hungary is a small European country but a good and sound hacking networks.\n It has closely beaten South Korea for the 10th spot. Hungarian hackers take the share of 1.4% in the global cyber crime activity.\n\n\n
        <b>------------------ THANK YOU -------------------</b>
    </string>
    <string name="text6">
      <b> SOME HACKING FACTS:-</b>\n\n
<b>FACTS:-</b>\n\n
#- 94% of malware is delivered via email.\n\n
#- Phishing attacks account for more than 80% of reported security incidents.\n\n
#- $17,700 is lost every minute due to phishing attacks.\n\n
#- 60 percent of breaches involved vulnerabilities for which a patch was available but not applied.\n\n
        #- 63 percent of companies said their data was potentially compromised within the last twelve months due to a hardware- or silicon-level security breach.\n\n
#- Attacks on IoT devices tripled in the first half of 2019.\n\n
#- fileless attacks grew by 256 percent over the first half of 2019.\n\n
#- Data breaches cost enterprises an average of $3.92 million.\n\n
#- 40 percent of IT leaders say cybersecurity jobs are the most difficult to fill.\n\n

<b>1. There is a hacker attack</b> every 39 seconds.\n
By the time the average person takes a selfie and uploads it to Instagram, the next hacker attack has already taken place.\n\n
<b>2. Cybercrime is more profitable</b> than the global illegal drug trade.\n\n
The profit from the illegal drug industry amounts to around $400 billion annually.\n For comparison, cybercriminals have earned a total of around $600 billion in 2018.\n\n
<b>3. Hackers steal 75 records</b> every second.\nCybersecurity facts show us the average number of record stolen per second. Breaches are actually a lot rarer than that – it’s just that each breach allows for a lot of records to be stolen.\n\n

<b>4. 66% of businesses attacked by hackers</b> weren’t confident they could recover.\n
Most businesses don’t really know if they’re prepared for a cyber attack. Actually, 75% of all businesses don’t even have a formal cyber attack response plan.\n\n
<b>5. 73% of black hat hackers said</b> traditional firewall and antivirus security is irrelevant or obsolete.\n
According to the same survey, 80% of hackers say “humans are the most responsible for security breaches”.\n\n
<b>6. The cybersecurity budget in the US</b> was $14.98 billion in 2019.\n
In just two years, the U.S. cybersecurity budget rose by almost 14%. It used to be just $13.15 billion in 2017.\n\n
<b>7. White hat hackers earned over $19 million</b> in bounties in 2018.\n
What’s interesting here is that 81% of them learned their craft mostly through blogs and educational materials online.\n Only 6% completed a formal class.\n\n
<b>8. There are over 715,000 cybersecurity experts</b> employed in the US alone.\n
There were 313,735 job openings for cybersecurity experts until August 2018.\n This number will continue to grow as we’ll see a bit later. Cybersecurity statistics assure us this will be one of the best paying jobs in the near future.\n\n
<b>9. Russian hackers can infiltrate</b> a computer network in 18 minutes.\nWant to reread the above stat? 18 minutes. I drink my morning coffee longer than that.
Russian hackers aren’t wasting any time when they put their mind to it.\n\n North Korean hackers need just under two and a half hours.\n Chinese ones take longer – about 4 hours.\n\n

<b>10. Hackers are the average American’s</b> biggest fear.\n
71% of Americans are wary of hackers stealing their credit card or financial info.\n Considering how many cyber attacks happen per day in the US, we can understand why that is.\n US citizens also worry about the possibility of identity theft – 67%.\n\n
<b>11. You can purchase a consumer account</b> for $1 on the dark market.\n
You can buy a bus ticket for a dollar. Or you can buy a ticket to an ecommerce site. The choice is yours.\n\n
<b>12. More than 6,000 online criminal marketplaces</b> sell ransomware products and services.\n
A total of 45,000 products are on sale there. If we add all non-ransomware products and services, the number will easily exceed 1 million.\n\n
<b>13. 444,259 ransomware attacks</b> took place worldwide in 2018.\n
Almost 1 in 4 (100,907) occurred within the consumer marketplace.\n\n
<b>14. Hackers create 300,000 new pieces</b> of malware daily.\n
I guess some people’s fingers never sleep. Let’s hope cybersecurity specialists are up to the task.\n\n
<b>15. There will be 3.5 million cybersecurity</b> jobs openings in 2021.\n
There are almost 314,000 job openings for cybersecurity specialists in the US alone as of October 2018. Cybersecurity Ventures expects that cybercrime will more than triple the number of job openings over the next five years.\n\n
<b>16. 65% of companies have over 1,000</b> stale user accounts.\n
Stale accounts and outdated permissions are targets for exploitation and malicious use. Hackers desire data, and they can get it by hijacking an account.\n\n

<b>17. 32% of black hat hackers admit</b> privileged accounts are their number one way to hack systems.\n
Seizing such an account could be pretty easy with a simple phishing attack.\n\n

<b>18. 75% of all attacked business</b> reported fraudulent emails.\n
Fraudulent emails as part of a phishing strategy are still a hacker’s favorite tool to obtain credentials.\n\n
<b>19. 15% of UK businesses lost control</b> over a network to a hacker.\n
Unauthorized use of systems, computers or servers from outside entities rose by 5% in 2018.\n\n
<b>20. Companies protect only</b> 3% of their folders.\n
And 88% of companies with over 1 million folders have over 100,000 folders open to everyone. Certainly makes a hacker’s job easier.\n\n
<b>21. 43% of UK businesses have reported</b> breaches or attacks in the last 12 months.\n
Cyber attack statistics show 72% of large companies report such events.\n\n
<b>22. Up until March 2019,</b> more than 14 billion data records had been lost or stolen.\n
The exact number as of March 27, 2019, was 14,717,618,286. Only 4% of these breaches were “Secure Breaches”, meaning the data was encrypted and therefore rendered useless.\n\n
<b>23. Yahoo’s data breach</b> – 3 billion compromised accounts.\n
It’s quite a story. In 2016 Yahoo admits the truth about the most significant data breach in history.\n They publicly state that 500 million users’ accounts were compromised in 2014.\n\n

<b>24. 209,000 payment card numbers</b> and expiration dates were stolen from Equifax.\n
146.6 million names, dates of birth and 145.5 million US social security numbers were taken as well from the credit monitoring firm.\n\n

<b>25. Marriot International</b> – 500 million users’ data stolen.\n
In 2018 Marriot International discovered attackers, who had remained in the system since 2014.\n\n The hackers stole the credit card numbers and expiration dates of more than 100 million customers. The other 400 million lost “only” some part of their private info – names, passport numbers.\n\n

<b>26. The cost of data breaches</b> will increase to $150 million in 2020.\n
As cloud adoption trends show, more and more businesses get interconnected, which means more targets become available. Not only that, the amount and importance of data stored online precludes the increased value that hackers can extract.\n\n

<b>27. Hackers siphoned off $13.4 million</b> from Cosmos Bank in India.\n
In 2018 Cybercriminals hacked the bank’s servers on August 11 and 13. The culprits stole the card details of around 12,000 Visa cards.\n\n

<b>28. The Carbanak gang of hackers</b> has stolen over $1 billion in total.\n
We can’t classify this as the biggest bank robbery in history, but it sure is interesting.\n They targeted around 100 banks around the world, and it took 2-4 months to siphon the money out from each one.\n\n The losses per bank were up to $10 million each. The cybercriminals started to test the Carbanak malware in 2013, and it’s still on the loose.\n\n

<b>29. Cybercrime cost the world</b> almost $600 billion in 2018.\n
This number amounts to 0.8% of the global GDP.
To acquire such amounts of money, black hat hackers need specific tools. You can’t find most of them just anywhere.\n\n

<b>30. 68% of black hat hackers say</b> multi-factor authentication and encryption are the biggest hacker obstacles.\n
The dark web can’t help you much with 2FA, but there’s a lot of stuff you can buy if you have some Bitcoins ready.\n\n

<b>31. For as low as $1.25 you</b> can get a Netflix account.\n
Netflix streaming is one of the standard hacking services and widely available. For a small fee, you’ll receive the email and password of someone’s Netflix account.\n\n
<b>32. You can purchase the WinPot</b> malware for 1 bitcoin.\n
Don’t know what WinPot does? Nothing much  It only makes the ATMs by a popular ATM vendor dispense all the cash from their cassettes.\n\n
<b>33. 92% of ATMs are vulnerable</b> to hacker attacks.\n
There are several ways to hack an ATM, but consider this – if your card data is stolen, then 100% of ATMs would be vulnerable to this kind of attack.\n\n
<b>34. The Tor network had more</b> than 2.2 million users in 2017.\n
The dark web hosted almost 60,000 unique onion domains, and around 57% of them hosted illegal content.\n\n
<b>35. You can become an American</b> citizen for $6,000.\n
You can also buy a fake passport + driving license + ID card from different countries if you can spare 700-900 euro. (approx. $787-$1010 at the exchange rate at the time of writing)\n\n

<b>36. Operation Cupcake:-</b>\n\n
In 2011 MI6 took down the instructions for bomb-making from an online al-Qaeda magazine and replaced them with recipes for cake.\n I guess the Taliban didn’t fall for it since there were no exploding muffins in the last eight years.\n\n
<b>37. #Lil’ Trump:-</b>\n\n
This is one of the hacking facts I’ll cherish in my memory. In 2013 Donald Trump’s Twitter account was hacked, and the hacker posted some Lil’ Wayne lyrics.\n\n
<b>38. Thunderstruck:-</b>\n\n
In 2012, Iran’s nuclear facilities were under cyberattack. The hackers forced workers at two of the nuclear facilities to listen to AC/DC’s Thunderstruck repeatedly at full volume. \nEven if you’re a fan, it can still annoy you at some point.\n\n

<b>39. Friendless Samy:-</b>\n\n
In 2005 Samy Kamkar took down MySpace. For our younger readers, MySpace was a social network like Facebook, only cooler.\n\n If someone shuts down Facebook now, it would be one of the biggest hacks of 2020. However, Samy didn’t want to shut down MySpace.\n\n All he wanted To achieve his dream he wrote a worm, exploiting a vulnerability in MySpace.\n\n

<b>40. The first hack:-</b>\n\n
In 1903 Guglielmo Marconi (the father of modern radio) was ready to transmit a message via the first wireless broadcasting technology.\n\n It used the same system as the telegraph. When he was prepared to send the message, the apparatus began to tap out a message in Morse code. The word was “RATS”, repeated over and over again.\n\n

    </string>

    <string name="text7">
        <b>HACKING TYPES:-</b>\nWe can segregate hacking into different categories, based on what is being hacked.\n\n<b>Here is a set of examples −</b>\n\n
        <b>1)- Website Hacking −</b> Hacking a website means taking unauthorized control over a web server and its associated software such as databases and other interfaces.\n\n
        <b>2)- Network Hacking −</b> Hacking a network means gathering information about a network by using tools like Telnet, NS lookup, Ping, Tracert, Netstat, etc.\nwith the intent to harm the network system and hamper its operation.\n\n
        <b>3)- Email Hacking −</b> It includes getting unauthorized access on an Email account and using it without taking the consent of its owner.\n\n
        <b>4)- Ethical Hacking −</b> Ethical hacking involves finding weaknesses in a computer or network system for testing purpose and finally getting them fixed.\n\n
        <b>5)- Password Hacking −</b> This is the process of recovering secret passwords from data that has been stored in or transmitted by a computer system.\n\n
        <b>6)- Computer Hacking −</b> This is the process of stealing computer ID and password by applying hacking methods and getting unauthorized access to a computer system.\n\n
        <b>Advantages of Hacking:-</b>\n
Hacking is quite useful in the following scenarios −\n\n
        <b>#- To recover lost information, especially in case you lost your password.</b>\n\n
        <b>#- To perform penetration testing to strengthen computer and network security.</b>\n\n
        <b>#- To put adequate preventative measures in place to prevent security breaches.</b>\n\n
        <b>#- To have a computer system that prevents malicious hackers from gaining access.</b>\n\n
<b>Disadvantages of Hacking:-</b>\n
Hacking is quite dangerous if it is done with harmful intent. It can cause −\n\n
        <b>#- Massive security breach.</b>\n\n<b>#- Unauthorized system access on private information.</b>\n\n<b>#- Privacy violation.</b>\n\n
        <b>#- Hampering system operation.</b>\n\n<b>#- Denial of service attacks.</b>\n\n <b>#- Malicious attack on the system</b>..\n\n\n
        <b>---------------- THANK YOU ---------------</b>
    </string>
<string name="text8">
        <b>HACKERS TYPE:-</b>\n\n
Hackers can be classified into different categories such as white hat, black hat, and grey hat, based on their intent of hacking a system.\n\n These different terms come from old Spaghetti Westerns, where the bad guy wears a black cowboy hat and the good guy wears a white hat.\n\n
    <b>1)- White Hat Hackers:-</b>
White Hat hackers are also known as Ethical Hackers. They never intent to harm a system, rather they try to find out weaknesses in a computer or a network system as a part of penetration testing and vulnerability assessments.\n\n
<b>Ethical hacking</b> is not illegal and it is one of the demanding jobs available in the IT industry. There are numerous companies that hire ethical hackers for penetration testing and vulnerability assessments.\n\n
    <b>2)- Black Hat Hackers:-</b>
Black Hat hackers, also known as crackers, are those who hack in order to gain unauthorized access to a system and harm its operations or steal sensitive information.\n\n
<b>Black Hat hacking</b> is always illegal because of its bad intent which includes stealing corporate data, violating privacy, damaging the system, blocking network communication, etc.\n\n
<b>3)- Grey Hat Hackers:-</b>
Grey hat hackers are a blend of both black hat and white hat hackers. They act without malicious intent but for their fun, they exploit a security weakness in a computer system or network without the owner’s permission or knowledge.\n\n
Their intent is to bring the weakness to the attention of the owners and getting appreciation or a little bounty from the owners.\n\n
<b>4)- Miscellaneous Hackers:-</b>
Apart from the above well-known classes of hackers, we have the following categories of hackers based on what they hack and how they do it −\n\n
<b>5)- Red Hat Hackers:-</b>
Red hat hackers are again a blend of both black hat and white hat hackers. They are usually on the level of hacking government agencies, top-secret information hubs, and generally anything that falls under the category of sensitive information.\n\n
<b>6)- Blue Hat Hackers:-</b>
A blue hat hacker is someone outside computer security consulting firms who is used to bug-test a system prior to its launch. They look for loopholes that can be exploited and try to close these gaps. Microsoft also uses the term BlueHat to represent a series of security briefing events.\n\n
<b>7)- Elite Hackers:-</b>
This is a social status among hackers, which is used to describe the most skilled. Newly discovered exploits will circulate among these hackers.\n\n
<b>8)- Script Kiddie:-</b>
A script kiddie is a non-expert who breaks into computer systems by using pre-packaged automated tools written by others, usually with little understanding of the underlying concept, hence the term Kiddie.\n\n
<b>9)- Neophyte:-</b>
A neophyte, "n00b", or "newbie" or "Green Hat Hacker" is someone who is new to hacking or phreaking and has almost no knowledge or experience of the workings of technology and hacking.\n\n
<b>10)- Hacktivist:-</b>
A hacktivist is a hacker who utilizes technology to announce a social, ideological, religious, or political message. In general, most hacktivism involves website defacement or denialof-service attacks.\n\n



    </string>
    <string name="text9">
        <b>BASIC COMMANDS:-</b>\n\n
<b>$ cmatrix:-</b>\n
Make matrix effect in termux .hacker look in termux.\n\n
<b>Installation :-</b>\n\n
After opening Termux First U have to update all the tools,  just type -\n
<b>$ apt update\n $ apt upgrade\n
$ apt install cmatrix\n
        type $ cmatrix\n\n</b>
        <b> Change Interface:-\n$ apt install git\n
$ git clone https://github.com/Cabbagec/termux-ohmyzsh\n\n
$ cd termux-ohmyzsh\n
$ chmod +x *\n\n
Run :\n\n
$ ./install.sh\n</b>
Now select theme = type number\n
select font = type number\n
Now your Termux interface hasbeen changed.\n\n
<b>$ cd ..</b>\n
Change current directory to parent directory.\n
<b>$ cd -</b>\n
Move one directory back from where you are now.\n\n
<b>$ cp-r</b>\n
Used to copy any directory [including hidden files]\n\n
<b>$ cp -f</b>\n
Force copy by removing the destination files if needed\n\n
<b>$ mv -f</b>\n
Force move by overwriting destination files without prompt\n\n
 <b>$ ifconfig -a</b>\n
Display the configuration of all interfaces, both active and inactive.\n\n
<b>$ ifconfig eth0</b>\n
Used to view the network settings on the interface eth0.\n\n
<b>$ ifconfig wlan0</b>\n
Used to view the network settings on wlan0.\n\n
<b>$ ifconfig eth1 up</b>\n
Used to active the network interface eth1.\n\n
<b>$ ifocnfig wlan0 down</b>\n
Used to deactive the network interface wlan0.\n\n
<b>$ ifconfig eth1 down</b>\n
Deactive the Network interface eth1.\n\n
<b>$ ifconfig wlan0 up</b>\n
Active the network interface wlan0.\n\n
<b>mv -v\n
To move any directory\n\n
$ mv [file1 name] [new file2 name]\n
to rename files file1 renames to file2.\n\n
$ Is\n
List current folder contents\n\n
$ ls -a\n
List of all files including hidden files.\n\n
$ ls -R\n
It shows recursively list of sub-directories\n\n
$ cat[file]\n
To display file information\n\n
$ nano [file]\n
To display and edit files.\n\n
$ wget\n
This command used to download any file from online source like github.\n\n
$ git clone [github url]\n
Used to clone any repository form github.\n\n
$ rm [file]\n
Used to remove/delete any files.\n\n
$ clear\n
To clear all the task on a terminal; means clear terminal.\n\n
$ uname -m\n
Used to find the architecture of your device.\n\n
$ cd [directory name]\n
Used to change directory.\n\n
$ ls\n
Used to Print the directory files.\n\n
$ ifconfig\n
It shows your network interface and local ip address.\n\n
$ pwd\n
It shows Your current working directory.\n\n
$ exit\n
This command is used to Exit from Terminal.\n\n</b>
    </string>
    <string name="text10">
       <b> PHISHING:-</b>
Phishing is the fraudulent attempt to obtain sensitive information such as usernames, passwords and credit card details by disguising oneself as a trustworthy entity in an electronic communication.\n\n Typically carried out by email spoofing or instant messaging,  it often directs users to enter personal information at a fake website which matches the look and feel of the legitimate site.\n\n
<b>1)- Shellphish:-</b>\n\n
Phishing Tool for 18 social media:\n <b>Instagram, Facebook, Snapchat, Github, Twitter, Yahoo, Protonmail, Spotify, Netflix, Linkedin, Wordpress, Origin, Steam, Microsoft, InstaFollowers, Gitlab, Pinterest.</b>\n\n

<b>#- Installation :-\n
After opening Termux First U have to update all the tools, just type -\n
$ apt update \n$ apt upgrade\n\n Install git, just type-\n
$ apt install git\n\n Now type\n
$ git clone https://github.com/thelinuxchoice/shellphish\n\n
Open the directory\n
$ cd shellphish\n\n
Run :\n
$ ./shellphish.sh\n\n
> select your option\n
it will generates phishing url . Now send this url to victem for phishing.\n\n</b>
<b>2)- Socialfish:-\n</b>
SocialFish ultimate phishing tool such as
Twitter, stackoverflow, wordpress, github, google, facebook.\n\n
        <b>#-Installation:-\n\n
Open and update the app\n
$ apt update\n $ apt upgrade\n\n
Then you have to install Git and python2 tools,Now type-\n
$ apt install git\n
$ apt install python2\n\n Then type-\n
$ git clone https://github.com/UndeadSec/SocialFish.git\n\n
$ cd SocialFish\n\n
Give permission\n
$ chmod +x *\n\n
$ pip2 install -r requirements.txt\n
usage :\n\n
$ python2 SocialFish.py\n</b>
Now select your target and it will generate an url using Ngrok.\n
then it send to victem..\n\n
<b>3)- Weeman:-</b>\n
Weeman is a phishing tool.\n\n
<b>#- Installation:-\n\n
$ apt update\n
$ apt upgrade\n\n
Then you have to install Git and python tools.\n
$ apt install git,\n Then type\n
$ apt install python2\n
$ git clone https://github.com/evait-security/weeman\n\n
$ cd weeman\n
Give permission\n
$ chmod +x *\n\n
usage :\n
$ python2 weeman.py\n
$ set url http://target.com\n
$ set action_url http://target.com\n
$ run.\n\n</b>

<b>4)-Blackeye:-</b>\n
The most complete Phishing Tool, with 32 templates +1 customizable.\n\n
<b>#- Installation :\n
        $ apt update\n
       $ apt upgrade\n\n
Then you have to install Git and curl tools.\n
$ apt install git\n
Then type\n
$ apt install curl\n\n
Now type\n
$ git clone https://github.com/thelinuxchoice/blackeye\n\n
$ cd blackeye\n
Then type\n
$ chmod +x * file name \n\n
Run :\n
$ bash blackeye.sh\n </b>
Now select your option it will generate an url for phishing..\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="text11">
        <b>SCANNING:-\n 1)- ViSQL:-</b>\n
viSQL= Scan SQL vulnerability on target site and sites of on server.\n\n
<b>#- Installation :\n\n
After opening Termux First U have to update all the tools,  just type -\n
        $ apt update \n$ apt upgrade\n\n
$ apt install git\n
$ apt install python2\n
$ apt install python\n
$ pip2 install requests\n\n
$ git clone https://github.com/blackvkng/viSQL.git\n\n
$ cd viSQL\n
$ pip2 install -r requirements.txt\n\n
Run :\n
$ python2 viSQL.py -help\n</b>
it shows options to use. very easy to use..\n\n\n

<b>2)-Router sploit:-</b>\n
RouterSploit Framework = scan the routers devices and check the vulnerabilities of Routers/Devices and exploits by the using frameworks.\nit consists of many more powerful modules for penetration testing operations.\n\n
<b>#- Installation:\n\n
Execute these commands one by one..\n
After opening Termux First U have to update all the tools,  just type -\n
$ apt update\n$ apt upgrade\n\n
$ apt install python\n
$ apt install python2\n\n
$ git clone https://github.com/reverse-shell/routersploit.git\n\n
$ cd routersploit\n\n
Now install These all packages step by step :-\n
$ pip2 install -r requirments-dev.txt\n
$ pip2 install -r requirments.txt\n
$ pip2 install request\n
$ pip2 install requests\n\n
Run routersploit:-\n
$ python2 rsf.py\n\n
$ rsf> show all\n
it shows all modules of rotersploit\n\n
$ rsf> use "module name"\n
it shows how you can use that module..\n\n\n</b>

<b>3)- Nikto:-</b>\nNikto is a web server assessment tool.\n
It is designed to find various default and insecure files,configurations and programs on any type of web server.\n\n
        <b>#- Installation:\n\n
After opening Termux First U have to update all the tools,  just type -\n
        $ apt update\n $ apt upgrade\n\n
$ apt install git\n
$ apt install perl\n
$ git clone https://github.com/sullo/nikto\n\n
$ cd nikto\n
$ chmod +x *\n\n
usage :\n
$ perl nikto.pl -H\n
it shows all options how you can use this tool .\n\n\n</b>
<b>4)- Click Jacking:-\n</b>
This script scans target site is vulnerable for this attack.\n\n
<b>#- Installation :-\n\n
After opening Termux First U have to update all the tools,  just type -\n
$ apt update \n$ apt upgrade\n\n
$ apt install git\n
$ apt install python2\n
$ apt install python\n\n
$ git clone https://github.com/D4Vinci/Clickjacking-Tester\n\n
$ cd Clickjacking-Tester\n
$ chmod +x *\n\n
Now create here file.txt file, in this file paste victem website and save it.\n
usage :\n
$ python3 Clickjacking-Tester.py file.txt\n\n</b>
Now it starts scanning if target is vulnerable then it shows you.\n\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="text12">
        <b>CRACKING:-</b>\n
Password cracking is the process of attempting to gain Unauthorized access to restricted systems using common passwords or algorithms that guess passwords.\n\n In other words, its an art of obtaining the correct password that gives access to a system protected by an authentication method..\n\n
<b>1)- HASHER:-</b>Hash cracker with auto detect hash in termux.\n
Hasher is a hash cracker tool that has supported more than 7 types of hashes.\n\n
support :-\n
md4\n md5\n sha1\n sha224\n sha256\n sha384\n sha512\n ripemd160\n whirlpool.\n
Execute these commands one by one to install.\n\n
<b>#- Installation :-\n\n
After opening Termux First U have to update all the tools,  just type -\n
$ apt update\n $ apt upgrade\n\n
Then you have to install Git , python and python2 tools.\n
$ apt install git\n
$ apt install python\n
Then type\n
$ apt install python2\n\n
Now type\n
$ git clone https://github.com/ciku370/hasher\n\n
Finally type\n
cd hasher\n\n
Run :\n
$ python2 hash.py.</b>\n
simply paste hashes. {hit enter}\n
it ask the type of hash . then select your type of hash to Decrypt it..\n\n\n

        <b>2)- Dost-attack:-</b>\n
Dost = WebServer Attacking Tools.\n\n
<b>#- Installation :-\n\n
$ apt update\n
$ apt upgrade\n\n
Then you have to install Git , python and python2 tools.\n
$ apt install git\n
$ apt install python2\n\n
Then type\n
$ apt install python\n\n
Now type\n
$ git clone https://github.com/verluchie/dost-attack\n\n
$ cd dost-attack\n\n
Give permission.\n
$ chmod 777 install.sh\n
Finally type\n
$ ./install.sh\n\n
Run :\n
$ ./dost\n</b>
It shows how you can use this tool.\n\n\n
<b>3)- Brutal :-</b>
Brutal = this is a toolkit to quickly create various payload,powershell attack, virus attack.\n\nand launch listener for a human interface devices..this is extreamly useful
for executing scripts on a target machin.\n\n
For use this tool you must install sudo in your termux. means it need rooted devices.\n\n
<b>#- Installation :-\n\n
$ apt update\n
$ apt upgrade\n\n
Now type\n
$ apt install git\n
$ git clone https://github.com/Screetsec/Brutal\n\n
Open the directory\n
$ cd Brutal\n\n
Now type\n
$ chmod +x *\n\n
Run :\n
$ sudo ./Brutal.sh\n</b>
Now simply select your option which you want.\n\n\n

<b>4)-Brutespray:-</b>\n
BruteSpray takes nmap GNMAP/XML output and automatically brute-forces services with default credentials using Medusa.\n
BruteSpray can even find non-standard ports by using the -sV inside Nmap.\n\n
<b>#- Installation :-\n\n
Update the app after opening\n
$ apt update\n
$ apt upgrade\n\n
Then you have to install Git and python2 tools.\n
$ apt install git\n\n
Then type\n
$ apt install python2\n\n
Now type\n
$ git clone https://github.com/x90skysn3k/brutespray\n\n
$ cd brutespray\n
Then type\n
$ pip2 install -r requirements.txt\n\n
usage :\n
$ python2 brutespray.py\n
First do an nmap scan with\n
-oG nmap.gnmap or -oX nmap.xml.\n\n
$ python2 brutespray.py -h\n
$ python brutespray.py -file nmap.gnmap\n
$ python brutesrpay.py -file nmap.xml\n
$ python brutespray.py -file nmap.xml -i..\n\n\n</b>

        <b>5)- Check url:-\n</b>
Check url = Detect evil urls that uses IDN Homograph Attack.\n\n
<b>#- Installation :-\n\n
$ apt update\n
$ apt upgrade\n\n
$ apt install git\n
$ apt install python2\n\n
$ apt install python\n
$ git clone https://github.com/UndeadSec/checkURL\n\n
$ cd checkURL\n
$ chmod +x *\n\n
usage :\n
Now run with python3 type this command :-\n
$ python3 checkURL.py -help\n\n
It shows all options.\n
$ python3 checkURL.py -url [attackerurl]\n\n</b>
attacker url = attacker url tom check this is idn evil url or original url.\n\n


    </string>
    <string name="text13">
      <b>1)- METASPLOIT:-</b>\n\n
If you wish to install the metasploit-framework all by itself You can use a shell script to install it.\n
remember dont turn off your internet connection.\n\n
follow these steps :-\n\n
        <b>#- Installation:-\n\n
1. open Termux app\n
2. run these commands-\n
After opening Termux First U have to update all the tools just type -\n\n
$ apt update\n
$ apt upgrade\n\n
Then you have to install wget tool.\n
Now type\n
$ apt install wget\n\n
5. clone metasploit with this command\n
$ wget https://Auxilus.github.io/metasploit.sh\n\n
Then type\n
$ bash metasploit.sh\n\n</b>
This script will install the latest version of metasploit-framework.\n
script also include some extras to make updating metasploit faster.\n\n
If all goes well, i.e. No red colored warnings, you can start metasploit using ./msfconsole.\n\n
Now take a coffe and sit down and wait 15-20 minutes to install metasploit in termux\n\n
after installation type this command :\n
<b>$ cd metasploit-framework\n
Now run msfconsole\n\n
$ ./msfconsole\n</b>
Enjoy metasploit..\n\n\n

<b>2)- A-Rate tool:-</b>\n
A-Rat = Remote access tool we can generate python based rat.\n\n
<b>installation :-\n\n
$ apt update \n $ apt upgrade\n\n
Then you have to install Git, python and python2 tools.\n
$ apt install git
Now type
$ apt install python2
$ apt install python\n\n
Then type\n
$ git clone https://github.com/Xi4u7/A-Rat\n\n
$ cd A-Rat\n
Give permission just type\n
$ chmod +x *\n\n
usage :\n
Finally type\n
$ python2 A-Rat.py\n\n
$ set host 127.0.0.1 [your ip]\n
$ set port 1337\n
$ set output /$HOME/rat.py\n\n
$ generate\n\n</b>
It generates rat.py in termux home directory\n
Open termux new session\n\n
<b>type $ ls\n
here you get that rat.py\n\n
go to again A-Rat means privious session of termux Type run to start exploit.\n
$ run\n\n
and then open new session and run rat like this\n
$ python rat.py\n\n </b>
and come back to A-Rat session\n
Now its connected to that rat. means Hacked.\n\n
press control + c to stop..\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="text14">
        <b>PASSWORD GENERATOR:-</b>\n\n
        A random password generator is software program or hardware device that takes input from a random or pseudo-random number generator and automatically generates a password.\n\n Random passwords can be generated manually, using simple sources of randomness such as dice or coins, or they can be generated using a computer or mobile.\n\n
<b>1)- Wordlist install:-\n\n</b>
Generateing wordlist using python.Execute these commands one by one to install sudo.\n\n
<b>#- Installation :-\n\n
After opening Termux First U have to update all the tools,  just type -\n
$ apt update\n
$ apt upgrade\n\n
Now you have to install python and wordlist.\n
$ apt install python..\n
$ pip install wordlist.\n\n
Then type\n
$ wordlist -h [to see all options]\n
Then type\n
$ wordlist -m 4 -M 6 -o wordlist.txt 12345678n\n\
Then type\n
$ -m = minimum length\n
$ -M = maximum length\n
wordlist.txt = to save all words\n\n
12345678 = here you can type alphabets also to make wordlist.\n
type this command : $ ls\n
here you get that file\n
name : wordlist.txt\n\n
now open this file type this command :-\n
$ cat wordlist.txt\n </b>
here you get all words means passwords list.\n\n\n.

<b>2)- Goblin-word generator:-</b>\n\n
Goblin word Generator tool is used to generate password list easily.
Execute These below commands one by one to install this tool..\n\n
<b>#- Installtion :-\n\n
Now type\n
$ apt update\n
$ apt upgrade\n\n
Then you have to install Git and python tools.\n
$ apt install git\n
Then type\n
$ apt install python \n\n
$ apt install python2\n
Now type\n
$ git clone https://github.com/UndeadSec/GoblinWordGenerator\n\n
Then open the directory\n
cd GoblinWordGenerator\n\n
To Give permission just type\n
$ chmod +x * file name.\n\n
usage :\n
$ python3 goblin.py\n\n</b>.
i want to generate list that length 4 to 6 then type here :\n $ 4:6 {hit enter}\n
Give name to your wordlist like, :\n $ pass.txt {hit enter}\n
and select option which you want and {hit enter} it will generate a pass.txt.\n
to open this file type this command :\n
$ cat pass.txt..\n\n\n

<b>3)- Password generator:-</b>\n\n
Password-GeneratorPassGen = is a tool which generates a custom passwords.
with 20+ char ,easy to remember and cannot be bruteforced.\n\n
# password cannot be brute forced\n
# it generates strong passwords\n
# easy to remember\n
# high entropy\n
# padding between the words\n
# custome names\n
# 20+ chracters\n\n
<b>#- Installation :-\n\n
Just update the termux\n
$ apt update\n
$ apt upgrade\n\n
Then you have to install Git and python tools.\n
Now type\n
$ apt install git\n
$ apt install python\n\n
Then type\n
$ git clone https://github.com/TechnicalMujeeb/PassGen\n\n
$ PassGen\n
$ chmod +x *\n\n
usage :\n
Then type\n
$ python passgen.py\n\n</b>
Now enter name : text\n
Now its generates passwords.\n
you guys can use these passwords in your accounts also..\n\n

    </string>
    <string name="text15">
<b>INFORMATION GATHERING:-</b>\n\n
When it comes to getting a clear information gathering concept, the simplest way to define it would be the process of collecting information about something you are interested in.\n\n
Collecting network data: Such as public, private and associated domain names, network hosts, public and private IP blocks, routing tables, TCP and UDP running services, SSL certificates, open ports and more.\n\n

<b>1)- Recon Dog:-</b>\n
Recon Dog is an all in one tool for all your basic information gathering needs.It uses APIs to gather all the information so your identity is not exposed.\n\n
<b>#- Installaion :-\n\n
After opening Termux First U have to update all the tools,  just type -\n
$ apt update\n
$ apt upgrade\n\n
Then you have to install Git and python2 tools.\n
$ apt install git\n
$ apt install python2\n\n
Then type\n
$ git clone https://github.com/UltimateHackers/ReconDog\n\n
$ cd ReconDog\n\n
Give permission\n
$ chmod +x *\n\n
usage :\n
$ python2 dog.py\n\n</b>
Now select your option which you want.\n\n\n

<b>2)- Angry fuzzer:-</b>\n
AngryFuzzer = Tools for information gathering Discover hidden files and directories on a web server.\n
The application tries to find url relative paths of the given website by comparing them with a given set.\n\n
Features:-\n
Fuzz url set from an input file.\n Concurrent relative path search.\n Configurable number of fuzzing workers.\n
Fuzz CMS ==> Wordpress,Durpal,Joomla.\n Generate reports of the valid paths.\n\n
<b>#- Installation :-\n\n
Open and update the app\n
$ apt update\n
$ apt upgrade\n\n
Then you have to install Git ,python and python2 tools.\n
$ apt install git\n
Then type\n
$ apt install python2\n\n
Now type\n
$ apt install python\n
$ git clone https://github.com/ihebski/angryFuzzer\n\n
$ cd angryFuzzer\n
$ pip2 install -r requirements.txt\n
$ pip2 install requests\n\n
Give permission just type\n
$ chmod +x *\n\n
Usage :\n
$ python2 angryFuzzer.py -h\n
It shows all options of this tool\n\n
$ python2 angryFuzzer.py -u http:site.com\n</b>
Now it starts collecting target information..\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="text16">
        <b>FIND VULNERABILITY:-</b>\n
        A vulnerability may also refer to any type of weakness in a computer system itself, in a set of procedures, or in anything that leaves information security exposed to a threat.\n\n

<b>1)- Striker:-</b>\n Striker = Striker is an offensive information and vulnerability scanner.\n\n
Features :\n
1.Check and Bypass Cloudflare\n
2.Retrieve Server and Powered by Headers\n
3.Fingerprint the operating system of Web Server\n
4.Detect CMS (197+ CMSs are supported)\n
5.Launch WPScan if target is using Wordpress\n
6.Retrieve robots.txt\n
7.Whois lookup\n
8.Check if the target is a honeypot\n
9.Port Scan with banner grabbing\n
10.Dumps all kind of DNS records\n
11.Generate a map for visualizing the attack surface.\n
12.Gather Emails related to the target.\n
13.Find websites hosted on the same web server.\n
14.Find hosts using google.\n
15.Crawl the website for URLs having parameters.\n
16.SQLi scan using online implemention of SQLMap.\n
17.Basic XSS scanning.\n\n\n
<b>#- Installation :-\n\n
After opening Termux First U have to update all the tools,  just type -\n
$ apt update\n $ apt upgrade\n\n
Then you have to install Git ,python and python2 tools.\n
$ apt install git\n
Then type\n
$ apt install python2\n\n
Now type\n
$ apt install python\n
$ git clone https://github.com/s0md3v/Striker\n\n
$ cd Striker\n
Now type\n
$ pip2 install -r requirements.txt\n\n
Run :\n\n
$ python2 striker.py\n</b>
it shows how you can use this tool.\n\n\n

        <b>2)- TM scanner:-</b>\n TM-scanner is simple python script.This tool for detecting vulnerabilities in websites.\n\n
<b>#- Installation :-\n\n
Open the app and update it, just type\n
$ apt update\n
$ apt upgrade\n\n
Then you have to install Git,python and python2 tools.\n
$ apt install git\n
Then type\n
$ apt install python2\n\n
Then type\n
$ apt install python\n
$ git clone https://github.com/TechnicalMujeeb/TM-scanner.\n\n
$ cd TM-scanner\n
Give permission\n
$ chmod +x *\n\n
Open the tool\n
$ sh install.sh\n\n
usage :\n
$ python2 tmscanner.py\n\n</b>
select your option and enter target site [example.com].\n\n\n

<b>3)- Red Hawk:-</b>\n
Red Hawk = All in one tool for Information Gathering and Vulnerability Scanning.\n\n
Scans That You Can Perform Using RED HAWK :-\n
1- Basic ScanWhois Lookup\n 2- Geo-IP Lookup\n 3- Grab Banners\n
       4- DNS Lookup\n 5- Subnet Calculator\n 6- Nmap Port Scan\n 7- Sub-Domain Scanner\n
8- Reverse IP Lookup and CMS Detection\n
9- Error Based SQLi Scanner\n
10- Bloggers View\n
11- WordPress Scan\n
12- Crawler\n
13- MX Lookup\n
14- Scan For Everything\n\n
<b>#- Insatallation :-\n\n
$ apt update\n
$ apt upgrade\n\n
Then you have to install Git and php tools.\n
$ apt install git\n
Then type\n
$ apt install php\n\n
Then type\n
$ git clone https://github.com/Tuhinshubhra/RED_HAWK\n\n
$ RED_HAWK\n
Give permission just type\n
$ chmod +x *\n\n
usage :\n
$ php rhawk.php\n </b>
Use the "help" command to see the command list\n\n
type in the domain name you want to scan (without Http:// OR Https://).\n
Select whether The Site Runs On HTTPS or not.\n
Select the type of scan you want to perform\n
Leave the rest to the scanner..\n\n\n

        <b>4)- Breacher:-</b>\n\n
An advanced multithreaded admin panel finder written in pythonA script to find admin login pages and EAR vulnerabilites.\n\n
Features:-
1.Multi-threading on demand.\n
2.Big path list (482 paths).\n
3.Supports php, asp and html extensions.\n
4.Checks for potential EAR vulnerabilites.\n
5.Checks for robots.txt.\n
6.Support for custom patns.\n\n
<b>#- Installation :\n\n
$ apt update\n
$ apt upgrade\n\n
Then you have to install Git, python and python2 tools.\n
$ apt install git\n
Then type\n
$ apt install python2\n\n
Now type\n
$ apt install python\n
Now type\n
$ git clone https://github.com/s0md3v/Breacher\n\n
$ cd Breacher\n
Run :\n
$ python2 breacher.py\n\n
Check all paths without threads\n
$ python2 breacher -u example.com.\n\n\n</b>

<b>5)- Wpseku tool:-</b>\n\n
We can find vulnerabilities in wordpress sites this is very usefull tool.\n\n
<b>#- installation :-\n\n
Open the app and update it.\n
$ apt update\n
$ apt upgrade\n\n
Then you have to install Git , python2 and python tools.\n
Now type\n
$ apt install git\n
$ apt install python2\n\n
Now type\n
$ apt install python\n
Then type\n
$ git clone https://github.com/m4110k/WPSeku\n\n
$ cd WPSeku\n
Give permission\n
$ chmod +x *\n\n
Finally type\n
$ pip install -r requirements.txt\n\n
usage :\n
$ python wpseku.py\n </b>
here all options are present to use this tool.\n\n
example :\n
$ python wpseku.py -url http:target.com..\n\n\n

<b>CMS MAP:-</b>\n\n
Cms map is a tool used to find the vulnerabilities of websites such as joomla,dripal,wordpress,
with the help of this tool we can scan our site vulnerabilities and fix it,and stay safe and secure.\n\n

<b>Installation :-\n\n
Open the app and update it just type\n
$ apt update\n
$ apt upgrade\n\n
Then you have to install Git and python2 tools.\n
$ apt install git\n
$ apt install python2\n\n
Then type\n
$ git clone https://github.com/Dionach/CMSmap.git\n\n
$ cd CMSmap\n
Give permission\n
$ chmod +x *\n\n
usage :-\n
    $ python2 cmsmap.py -h\n\n </b>
[it shows all options how we can use this tool].\n\n

    </string>
    <string name="text17">
        <b>PENETRATION TESTING:-</b>
A penetration test, colloquially known as a pen test, pentest or ethical hacking, is an authorized simulated cyberattack on a computer system, performed to evaluate the security of the system.\n\n
<b>1)- Sublist3r:-</b>\n\n
Sublist3r = Fast subdomains enumeration tool for penetration testers .It helps penetration testers and bug hunters.\n
        collect and gather subdomains for the domain they are targeting.\n\n
<b>#- Installation :-
After opening Termux First U have to update all the tools, just type -\n
$ apt update\n
$ apt upgrade\n\n
Then you have to install Git and python2 tools.\n
Now type\n
$ apt install git\n
$ apt install python2\n\n
Then type\n
$ git clone https://github.com/aboul3la/Sublist3r\n\n
$ cd Sublist3r\n\n
Now type\n
$ pip2 install requirements.txt\n
Then type\n
$ pip2 install requests\n\n
Run :-\n
$ python2 sublist3r.py\n
$ python2 sublist3r.py -h \n </b>
it shows all options, how you can use this tool\n
$ python2 sublist3r.py -d site.com\n
-d = domain name.\n\n\n

<b>2)- Gloom framework:- </b>\n\n
Gloom-Framework = Linux Penetration Testing Framework ,Execute these commands one by one to install this tool.\n
works in rooted devices Remember you have must installed sudo in Termux.\n\n
<b>#- Installation :-\n\n
$ apt update\n
$ apt upgrade\n\n
now you have to install git,python and python2.\n
$ apt install git\n
now type\n
$ apt install python2\n
$ apt install python\n\n
now install nmap and tsu.\n
$ apt install nmap\n
$ apt install tsu\n\n
$ git clone https://github.com/StreetSec/Gloom-Framework.git\n\n
$ cd Gloom-Framework\n
$ chmod +x *\n\n
$ sudo python2 install.py\n
$ sudo python2 gloom.py\n
$ pip2 install requests\n\n
if you get error for bs4 and beautifulsoup then simply type\n
$ sudo pip2 install bs4\n
$ sudo pip2 install beautifulsoup\n\n
Run :\n
$ sudo python2 gloom.py\n\n</b>
[gloom] help\n
it shows all modules to use any module simply copy and paste that module name..\n\n\nn

<b>3)- Cyber-scan:-</b>\n\n
CyberScan is an open source penetration testing tool.\n
that can analyse packets , decoding , scanning ports, pinging and geolocation of an IP including (latitude, longitude , region , country ..)\n\n
<b>Installation :-\n\n
First update the termux just type\n
$ apt update\n
$ apt upgrade\n\n
Then you have to install Git and python tools.\n
$ apt install git\n
Then type\n
$ apt install python2\n\n
Now type\n
$ apt install python\n
$ git clone https://github.com/medbenali/CyberScan.git\n\n
$ cd CyberScan\n\n </b>
<b>usage :\n
$ python2 CyberScan.py -v\n
$ CyberScan -h\n\n
We can perform ping operations with several protocols using CyberScan The fastest way to discover hosts on a local Ethernet network
        is to use ARP:-\n\n
$ python2 CyberScan -s 192.168.1.0/24 -p arp\n
In case when ICMP echo requests are blocked, we can still use TCP:\n
$ CyberScan -s 192.168.1.105 -p tcp -d 80\n </b>
192.168.1.105 = target IP..\n\n\n

<b>4)- D-tect:-</b>\n\n
D-TECT is an All-In-One Tool for Penetration Testing.\n This is specially programmed for Penetration Testers and Security Researchers
        to make their job easier, instead of launching different tools for performing different task.\n\n D-TECT provides multiple
features and detection features which gather target information and finds different flaws in it.\n\n
Features:-\n\n
# Sub-domain Scanning\n
# Port Scanning\n
# Wordpress Scanning\n
# Wordpress Username Enumeration\n
# Wordpress Backup Grabbing\n
# Sensitive File Detection\n
# Same-Site Scripting Scanning\n
# Click Jacking Detection\n
# Powerful XSS vulnerability scanning\n
# SQL Injection vulnerability scanning\n
User-Friendly UI\n\n
<b>Installation :\n\n
Open the termux and type\n
$ apt update\n
$ apt upgrade\n\n
Then you have to install Git and python2 tools.\n
$ apt install git\n
$ apt install python2\n\n
Then type\n
$ git clone https://github.com/shawarkhanethicalhacker/D-TECT\n\n
Then type\n
$ cd D-TECT\n\n
$ chmod +x *\n
Then type\n
$ pip2 install requests\n\n.
usage :\n
$ python2 d-tect.py\n </b>
Now select your options to use that particular tool..\n\n\n

<b>5)- Pureblood:-</b>\n\n
A Penetration Testing Framework created for Hackers / Pentester / Bug HunterWeb Pentest Information Gathering.\n\n
        <b>Installation :-\n\n
$ apt update\n
$ apt upgrade\n\n
Then you have to install Git, python and python2  tools.\n
$ apt install git\n
$ apt install python2\n
$ apt install python\n\n
Then type\n
$ git clone https://github.com/cr4shcod3/pureblood\n\n
$ cd pureblood\n\n
Give permission by type\n
$ chmod +x * file\n
$ pip install -r requirements.txt\n\n
Run :\n
$ python2 pureblood.py\n </b>
Now select your option, this tool will guide you..\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="text18">
<b>1)- Lazymux:-</b>\n\n
Lazymux is python based tool in this tool and collection of tools for termux users.
you guys can install some tools by typing number in easiest way.\n\n
<b>#- Installation :-\n\n
After opening Termux First U have to update all the tools,  just type -\n
$ apt update\n
$ apt upgrade\n\n
Then you have to install Git and python2 tools.\n
Now type\n
$ apt install git\n
$ apt install python2\n\n
Then type\n
$ git clone https://github.com/Gameye98/Lazymux\n\n
Open the directory just type\n
$ cd Lazymux\n
$ chmod +X *\n\n
usage :\n
$ python2 lazymux.py\n</b>
Now simply type the number of tool to install that particular tool in termux.\n\n\n

        <b>2)- Darkfly :-</b>
DarkFly-Tool is an installation tool for installing tools.You only have to choose the number.\n which tool you want to install. there are 530 tools ready for intall.\n\n
there are 7 SMS spam tools that are ready to use, you just need to choose spam to use the target number.\n
now it supports Linux OS and can be installed on ubuntu and termux, even though I only combine it.\n\n
<b>#- Installation :-\n\n
Open and update the app\n
$ apt update\n
$ apt upgrade\n\n
Now type\n
$ apt install git\n
Then type\n
$ git clone https://github.com/Ranginang67/DarkFly-Tool\n\n
Open the directory\n
$ cd DarkFly-Tool\n\n
Give permission\n
$ chmod +x *\n
$ sh install\n\n
Run :\n
$ DarkFly</b>\n
Now select your optoion, it will install your selected tool .\n\n\n

<b>3)- Installerv3:-\n\n</b>
        <b>#- Installation:-\n\n
$ apt update\n
$ apt upgrade\n\n
Then you have to install Git , php , curl, Ruby, figlet ,python2, lolcat tools..\n
Now type\n
$ apt install git\n
$ apt install php\n\n
Then type\n
$ apt install curl\n
Then type\n
$ apt install ruby\n\n
Now type\n
$ apt install figlet\n
Then type\n
$ apt install python2\n\n
Now type\n
$ gem install lolcat\n
$ git clone https://github.com/TUANB4DUT/TOOLSINSTALLERv3\n\n
$ cd TOOLSINSTALLERv3\n
Give permission\n
$ chmod +x TUANB4DUT.sh\n
$ sh TUANB4DUT.sh..\n\n </b>
    </string>
    <string name="text19">
        <b>LOCATION TRACKING:-</b>\n\n
Location tracking refers to technologies that physically locate and electronically record and track the movement of people or objects.\n\n Location tracking technology is in use every day with GPS navigation, locations located on digital pictures and searching for businesses nearby using common apps or any other hacking tools.\n\n

<b>1)- GPS:- </b>\n\n
GPS is the best way to track original exact location of a victim or friend.\n
But, Sometime this tool link not work perfectly.\n\n
<b>#- Installation:-\n\n
Open your termux\n
        $ apt update\n $ apt upgrade\n\n
$ Pkg install php \n $ Pkg install git\n
$ git clone https://github.com/indosecid/gps_tracking \n\n
        Now go to the directory of gps gracking and run \n
5. $ php gps php\n
Note that this tool is under progress.\n\n\n
<b>2)- Map viewer:-</b>\n\n
Map viewr shows map in termux\n
$ apt update\n
$ apt upgrade\n\n
To display world map in termux terminal\n
Type this command :\n
$ telnet mapscii.me \n\n</b>
press a = zoomin\n
press z = zoom out\n
press c = to quite\n
use arrow keys to goto left right up down..\n\n\n

<b>3)- IP Geo location:-</b>\n Retrieve IP Geolocation information.\n\n
<b>Geolocation Information :\n\n</b>
1.ASN\n 2.City\n 3.Country\n 4.Country Code\n 5.ISP\n 6.Latitude\n 7.Longtitude\n 8.Organization\n 9.Region Code\n 10.Region Name\n 11.Timezone\n 12.Zip Code.\n\n
<b>#- Installation :-\n\n
After opening Termux First U have to update all the tools,  just type -\n
$ apt update\n
$ apt upgrade\n\n
$ apt install git\n
$ apt install python\n
$ git clone https://github.com/maldevel/IPGeoLocation\n\n
$ cd IPGeoLocation\n
$ chmod +x *\n
$ pip install -r requirements.txt\n\n
Usage :\n
$ python ipgeolocation.py -t [target ip]\n</b>
it gives you all information related to your target..\n
Now you can trace Any Phone Number in Termux with the help of PhoneInfoga..\n\n\n

<b>4)- PhoneInfoga Tool:-</b>\n
After installation just type below commands to start using The Tool\n\n

        <b>#- Installation:- \n\n
Firstly type below command in termux\n
$ apt update\n $ apt upgrade\n\n
Then type\n
 $ pkg install python\n
 $ pkg install git\n\n
Now type\n
 $ git clone https://github.com/sundowndev/PhoneInfoga.\n\n
$ cd PhoneInfoga\n\n
 $ ls\n
 python -m pip install -r requirements.txt\n
 cp config.example.py config.py\n\n
Finally type\n
$ python phoneinfoga.py -n number\n </b>
you will get all the info regarding to the phone number..\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="text20">
        <b>BOMBING TOOLS:-</b>\n\n
<b>1)- TBomb:-</b>\n Use it only for fun. After opening Termux First U have to update all the tools,  just type -\n\n
<b>#- Installation:-\n\n
        $ apt update\n
$ apt upgrade\n\n
Then you have to install Git , python and python2 tools..\n
Now type\n\n
$ apt install git\n
Then type\n
$ apt install python2\n\n
$ apt install python\n
Now type\n
$ git clone https://github.com/TheSpeedX/TBomb\n\n
Open the directory\n
$ cd TBomb\n\n
Give permission\n
$ chmod +x *\n\n
Finally type\n
$ ./TBomb.sh\n</b>
Now select ur victem number and enjoy.\n\n\n

<b>2)- Termux make Call:-</b>\n
First you need to install these apps from playstore.\n\n
1] Termux App\n
2] Termux API App\n
Now open Termux and follow these steps.\n\n
<b>Installation :-\n\n
After opening Termux First U have to update all the tools,  just type -\n
$ apt update\n
$ apt upgrade\n\n
$ apt install termux-api\n
call process :-\n
$ termux-telephony-call 9999999999\n</b>
9999999999 = number of victem..\n\n

<b>3)- Termux send Sms :-</b>
Send sms using termux app\n
first you need to install these apps from playstore.\n\n
1] Termux App\n
2] Termux API App\n
Now open Termux and follow these steps\n\n

<b>Installation :-\n\n
After open Termux First U have to update all the tools,  just type -\n
$ apt update\n
$ apt upgrade\n\n
$ apt install termux-api\n
message sending process :-\n
$ termux-sms-send -n 9999999999 text\n\n</b>
9999999999 = Receiver number\n
text = your message here..\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="text21">
<b>SQL MAP:-</b>\n\n
SQL injection is a code injection technique that might destroy your database.\nSQL injection is one of the most common web hacking techniques.\n\n
SQL injection is the placement of malicious code in SQL statements, via web page input.\n\n

<b>1)- SQL MAP:-</b>\n\n
Sqlmap is an open source penetration testing tool.\n
that automates the process of detecting and exploiting, SQL injection flaws and taking over of database servers.\n\n
<b>#- Installation :-\n\n
After opening Termux First U have to update all the tools,  just type -\n\n
$ apt update\n
$ apt upgrade\n\n
Than you have to install Git ,Python,Python2 just type-\n
$ apt install git\n
$ apt install python2\n\n
$ apt install python\n
$ git clone https://github.com/sqlmapproject/sqlmap\n\n
Than you have to open the directory by typing below command-\n
$ cd sqlmap\n\n
Then you have to give permission to the file, just type\n
$ chmod +x * file name.\n\n
To Run the tool You have to type below command-\n
$ python2 sqlmap.py -h or \n
$ ./sqlmap.py \n\n </b>
It shows all options to use this tool sqlmap\n\n\n

<b>2)- SQliscan:-</b>\n\n
<b>#- Installation :-\n\n
After opening Termux First U have to update all the tools,  just type -\n
$ apt update\n
$ apt upgrade\n\n
$ apt install git\n
$ apt install curl\n
$ git clone https://github.com/thelinuxchoice/sqliscan\n\n
$ cd sqliscan\n
$ chmod +x *\n\n
usage :-\n
$ ./sqliscan.sh \n\n </b>
Now enter your dorks it will start collecting all vulnerable sites related to your dork and also these sites saved in saved.txt file.\n\n\n

<b>3)- ViSQL:-</b>\n
viSQL = Scan SQL vulnerability on target site and sites of on server.\n\n
<b>#- Installation :-\n\n
After opening Termux First U have to update all the tools,  just type -\n
$ apt update\n
$ apt upgrade\n\n
Then you have to install Git, python and python2  tools.\n
$ apt install git\n\n
$ apt install python2\n
$ apt install python\n\n
Now type\n
$ pip2 install requests\n
$ git clone https://github.com/blackvkng/viSQL.git\n\n
$ cd viSQL\n
$ pip2 install -r requirements.txt\n\n
Run :\n
$ python2 viSQL.py -help\n\n </b>
it shows options to use. very easy to use.\n
    </string>
    <string name="text22">
        <b>Youtube Video Links:-This video links will help you to learn many types of hacking  </b>\n\n
        <b>1)- Install Metasploit in Termux:-</b>\n\nhttps://youtu.be/lEsIteAAZOU\n\n
<b>2)- Password generator tool:-</b>\n\nhttps://youtu.be/1tXGAmAzyk8\n\n
<b>3)- Phishing Social media :-</b>\n\nhttps://youtu.be/CJdChYryTLk\n\n
        <b>4)- Flood Attack On Android:-</b>\n\nhttps://youtu.be/pwZqRr13lLs\n\n
<b>5)- Lazymux Tool:-</b>\n\nhttps://youtu.be/mwVE1_1_DaA.\n\n
<b>6)- Hack Free fire:-</b>\n\nhttps://youtu.be/g22uxjfm2CA\n\n
<b>7)- Darkfly Tool For Termux:-</b>\n\nhttps://youtu.be/QUtw_x-fOgo..\n\n
<b>8)- Bombing In Termux:-</b>\n\nhttps://youtu.be/etakUuwX5j0\n\n
<b>9)- Location Tracking Tool:-</b>\n\nhttps://youtu.be/-YuoVIJVEKA\n\n
<b>10)- Shellphish Install:-</b>\n\nhttps://youtu.be/-CMs-8IQjH0\n\n
<b>11)- Dangerous XploitSpy Tool:-</b>\n\nhttps://youtu.be/qQgqwFxdx1E\n\n
<b>12)- Hack phone with IP Address:- </b>\n\nhttps://youtu.be/VR0ttyEcCMY\n\n
<b>13)- Information Gathering tool:-</b>\n\nhttps://youtu.be/PKbX0DeidSc\n\n
<b>14)- Blackeye Tools Netflix, Facebook Hack:-</b>\n\nhttps://youtu.be/EuUIOvECfhM\n\n
<b>15)- HiddenEye on Termux:-</b>\n\nhttps://youtu.be/Hv7PLzEZ1Eo\n\n
<b>16)- WhatsApp Hack otp Bypass:-</b>\n\nhttps://youtu.be/PM72UhPjf1A\n\n
<b>17)- Brute Force Attack tool:-</b>\n\nhttps://youtu.be/mgRT4muVb4o\n\n
<b>18)- WhatsApp Hack:-</b>\n\n https://youtu.be/bo3TF2C1IqE\n\n
<b>19)- Information Collection tool:-</b>\n\nhttps://youtu.be/W78qGCE0N58\n\n
<b>20)- Matrix Effect on Termux:-</b>\n\nhttps://youtu.be/2t-wxsuhLLs\n\n
<b>21)- Figlet Cool fonts :-</b>\n\nhttps://youtu.be/j9UM7VNfpJk\n\n
<b>22)- Using Nano tools:-</b>\n\nhttps://youtu.be/SdIZZmO2RQE\n\n
<b>23)- Port Forwarding using NGROK:-</b>\n\nhttps://youtu.be/XQqzoz2le64\n\n
<b>24)- Install Kali linux tools :-</b>\n\nhttps://youtu.be/kAiBZqF8kTA\n\n
<b>25)- Goblin Word Generator:-</b>\n\nhttps://youtu.be/SYUkzleiX7k\n\n
<b>26)- Android Hacking:-</b>\n\nhttps://youtu.be/Xq9aHIjZtJ8\n\n
<b>27)- PhoneSploit Tool:-</b>\n\nhttps://youtu.be/BNfsKevry8M\n\n
<b>28)- All in One TxTool:-</b>\n\nhttps://youtu.be/7wcPkOIvyD4\n\n
<b>29)- Basic Command:-</b>\n\nhttps://youtu.be/V3_B-3nmrPU\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="text23"> <b> ______ -: SOME INTERESTING AND FUNNY TOOLS:- ______</b>\n\n
        <b>(1) Fire In Termux:-\n\n $ apt install libcaca\n
    $ cacafire..\n\n
 (2) Running Train in Termux:-\n\n
  $ apt install sl\n
   $ sl\n\n
   (3) Matrix In Termux:-\n\n
  $ apt install cmatrix\n
   $ cmatrix\n\n
 (4) Web Surfing in Termux:-\n\n
   $ apt install w3m\n
   $ w3m Google.com\n\n
 (5) Cow Saying in Termux:-\n\n
   $ apt install cowsay\n
  $ cowsay "any text"\n\n
     (6) Essay in Termux:-\n\n
   $ apt install fortune\n
  $ fortune\n\n
 (7) Colorful text in Termux:-\n\n
   $ apt install toilet\n
   $ toilet hello\n\n
 (8) Remember Any Command in Termux:-\n\n
  $ apt install fish\n
   $ fish\n\n
 (9) Check IP in Cowsay style:-\n
  $ ipconfig | cowsay\n\n
 (10) To Reverse Digits\n
            $ rev\n\n</b>


    </string>
    <string name="text24">
        <b>TERMUX GUIDE:-</b>This tutorial has been prepared for educational purpose to gain knowledge about hacking and How to protect yourself from Hackers.\n\n

you are here that means you want to learn Hacking. Most welcome, you are in the right place.\n\n
        In this tutorial you will get important tools and all the packages with their work.\n You can learn how to install them.\n\n
        <font color="blue">
            <b> APP Version- 1.0\n
                Build Version- 29.0.3\n\n</b> </font>
        <b> Developed By- Viratian Sourav</b>(A computer Engineer student).\n\n
        <b>If this tutorial little bit help you, Please rate this App.</b>
    </string>
    <string name="text25"></string>
    <string name="text26"></string>


</resources>
